(Penny:)No. We're always doing
what you guys want.
(Penny:)Just once, it'd be nice
if you did something we wanted.
(Sheldon:)You want to be green?
(Leonard:)You know, they
really have tried to like
(Leonard:)a lot of the same stuff
we're into.
Yeah, we do game
(Penny:)nights and video game
nights and we watch movies
(Penny:)with director's commentary.
Oh, my favorite--
George Lucas can talk
(Amy:)all the way through
Star Wars, I say one word
(Amy:)and I'm banished
to the kitchen.
(Penny:)Yeah, today Amy and I
are deciding
(Penny:)what we're all gonna do.
(Leonard:)You got it, you girls
are in charge.
(Penny:)Thank you.
Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Now that we're not playing,
you can be green.
(Penny:)Thank you.
And since you're green
(Sheldon:)this time, I can
be it next time.
(Penny:)All right, let's see.
What's something fun
(Penny:)the guys would
never take us to do?
(Penny:)Oh, I know-- we could
go horseback riding.
(Amy:)I actually can't.
(Amy:)My hips don't open
wider than 22 degrees.
(Amy:)I rode a very
thin pony once.
(Amy:)On the first bump...
just popped right off.
(Penny:)All right, well,
what do you want to do?